

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **Details**

Barcelona, Spain +49 1522 578 1249 noahjadallah@outlook.de

DATE OF BIRTH 02.02.2000

NATIONALITY German

### Links

Portfolio

LinkedIn

GitHub

### Skills

**Web Development** 

Node.js, React/Next.js, Redux, Express.js, GraphQL, Tailwind CSS, HTML5/JS/CSS

## ML/DS

Python, Numpy, Pandas, Keras, PyTorch

### Other

Java, SQL, R

Continuous Integration (Git), Analytical Thinking, Architecture Design

### Languages

German C2

English C1-C2

French A2

Arabic A2

## **Hobbies**

Cooking, Sports, Music

# **Profile**

Creative thinking **Software Engineer** with **5 years of programming experience**, with deeper knowledge in designing and developing **full-stack web applications**. Confident communicator who has proven to work well in teams and to stay cheerful and calm in stressful situations. Fast learner and able to adapt to a changing environment. Looking for a **full-time position** as a **Full-Stack, Frontend** or **Backend Software Engineer** to continue my journey in the professional tech world.

# **Work Experience**

Software Developer at Qualicen GmbH, Munich, Germany (Remote)

SEPTEMBER 2022 — PRESENT

• Working on an analytics web app (Java, Node.js) in an agile environment.

## **Co-Founder and Developer at Flash AIO**

JANUARY 2021 — PRESENT

- Co-Founded and developed a Software as a Service (SaaS) company that helps users secure highly sought-after collector's items.
- Developed cross-platform Electron app and worked on integrations for Discord and Stripe.
- Implemented a custom license key and user management solution.
- Acquired over 70 monthly paying customers.

### Intern at Thaltegos GmbH, Munich, Germany

SEPTEMBER 2022 — MARCH 2022

- Designed software architecture and developed a new SaaS in the E-Mobility Sector (Node.js, React, GraphQL, SQL).
- Improved the quality of data of over 50k EV charging points by utilizing various ML techniques through KNIME.

## Freelancer, Munich, Germany

MAY 2019 — SEPTEMBER 2020

- Developed websites and web apps for multiple clients.
- Handled client acquisition and communication.

# **Education**

MSc Fundamental Principles of Data Science, Universitat de Barcelona, Barcelona, Spain

SEPTEMBER 2022 — JULY 2022 Current average grade: 8.5/10

BSc Information Systems, Technical University Munich, Munich, Germany
SEPTEMBER 2018 — AUGUST 2021

Final Grade: 2.3 | Thesis Grade: 1.0 (Thesis as PDF)

Abitur, German International School Dubai, Dubai, UAE

SEPTEMBER 2012 — JULY 2018

Final Grade: 1.6

# **Extra-curricular activities**

Student's Representative at German International School Dubai, Dubai, UAE SEPTEMBER 2016 — JULY 2017

References available upon request